{
    "subject": "resource/One_Night_at_McCool's",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "One Night at McCool's is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9335529208183289,
            "question": "Is 'One Night at McCool's' considered a documentary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8382970690727234,
            "question": "How popular was the film genre 'One Night at McCool's' during its time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8265075087547302,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of another film in the same genre as 'One Night at McCool's'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8010698556900024,
            "question": "What genre is 'One Night at McCool's'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.761283814907074,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films like 'One Night at McCool's'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7491452693939209,
            "question": "What impact has the film genre 'One Night at McCool's' had on popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5748820900917053,
            "question": "Has the genre of 'One Night at McCool's' evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29278308153152466,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors who have starred in films of this type?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25612494349479675,
            "question": "What are some notable characteristics of films belonging to this genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14643479883670807,
            "question": "Can you name a director known for making films in this genre?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=One Night at McCool's is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4949_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable characteristics of films belonging to this genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4949_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors who have starred in films of this type?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4949_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has the genre of 'One Night at McCool's' evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4949_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4949_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents describe \"One Night at McCool's\" as a movie with various actors, providing plot details that clearly indicate it is a film. Therefore, the statement \"One Night at McCool's is a type of Film\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}